<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Cayman</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Cayman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Location quotient LQ. A  Spatial concentration perspective.</title>
      <link>/katex-math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/katex-math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>Here a relative concentration measure, the location quotient LQ, is estimated to evaluate the diabetes epidemic trend in time by state and border region.
The quotient may take two relevant values: LQ &amp;gt; 1, which indicates that diabetes deaths cases are higher in state j relative to the national level.
Whereas values LQ &amp;lt;1 indicate a lower proportion in state i, relative to the national level.
Using this relative measure allows controlling the population size in every state, to determine diabetes deaths concentration among different geographic areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasas de Mortalidad Ajustadas por Estructura edad.</title>
      <link>/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>{&#34;x&#34;:{&#34;data&#34;:[{&#34;x&#34;:[31,30,32,29,28,26,21,27,23,24,25,15,17,19,14,18,22,16,12,11,20,13,10,5,7,4,6,9,8,2,3,1],&#34;y&#34;:[113,112,107,103,98,97,96,90,89,87,85,81,81,79,78,77,76,76,74,74,74,71,69,68,67,67,65,63,59,59,59,53],&#34;text&#34;:[&#34;reorder(Estado, Tasa): Puebla
Tasa: 113
Sexo: Hombre
Tasa: 113&#34;,&#34;reorder(Estado, Tasa): Tlaxcala
Tasa: 112
Sexo: Hombre
Tasa: 112&#34;,&#34;reorder(Estado, Tasa): Tabasco
Tasa: 107
Sexo: Hombre
Tasa: 107&#34;,&#34;reorder(Estado, Tasa): Guanajuato
Tasa: 103
Sexo: Hombre
Tasa: 103&#34;,&#34;reorder(Estado, Tasa): Morelos
Tasa: 98
Sexo: Hombre
Tasa: 98&#34;,&#34;reorder(Estado, Tasa): México
Tasa: 97
Sexo: Hombre
Tasa: 97&#34;,&#34;reorder(Estado, Tasa): CDMX
Tasa: 96
Sexo: Hombre
Tasa: 96&#34;,&#34;reorder(Estado, Tasa): Veracruz
Tasa: 90
Sexo: Hombre</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crecimiento de la mortalidad por Diabetes en México, 20 años de cambios.</title>
      <link>/cayman-typography/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cayman-typography/</guid>
      <description>## [1] 8.45During the last fifteen years, T2D mortality showed an explosive pattern at the border states. This growth rate pattern departs from the trend followed by all other death causes.
In particular, a rapid growth trajectory at the southern border is evident, with a widening gap by the end of the study period. This trend reaches a 169% increase in Quintana Roo by 2019 relative to the base year 1998, with an annual 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Images</title>
      <link>/nasa-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nasa-images/</guid>
      <description>The below images are from the NASA Image and Video Library &amp;ndash; indulge yourself, revel in their beauty. Also, the built-in figure shortcode is shown for each image.
{{&amp;lt; figure img=&amp;quot;sun.jpg&amp;quot; caption=&amp;quot;The Sun is the star at the center of the Solar System. It is a nearly perfect sphere of hot plasma, with internal convective motion that generates a magnetic field via a dynamo process. It is by far the most important source of energy for life on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>